I've done a rough sketch with the pen.
I'm now going to work over that, with black acrylic paint.
Most of the paint I've used for the walls and the murals is actually just a standard interior eggshell, which I got from the paint store.
As you know you can get any color mixed up that you like, so I had a variety of colors that I worked with.
When I want to go into details, then I use my acrylic paints for the bright red flowers, and the blues and the black on the tiger.
I understand that, I just don't do it.
I paint the way I feel intuitively that I should go.
So in this section I want to do the tiger first.
Yes, when I start painting behind, I may overlap onto the black, but that's okay, then I'll paint the black again.
It's my particular method, and I said earlier, I have a tendency to paint in strange ways, I don't follow the norm.
But this is the way I do it.
And I think my point here is that I celebrate my way.
So, anybody else's way I also celebrate, as long as they don't try to tell me to do it there way.
I'm not trying to tell anybody to do it my way, I'm just showing you what I do.